Richard York Gallery
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Artists' Artwork Files, circa 1865-2004, Series 2:; (Boxes 7-64; 56.85 linear feet)
  - General, circa 1865-2004, 2.1:
    - Martin, Homer Dodge, 106CY: South Side, Long Island, 1982-1984 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Martin, Homer Dodge, 1186CY: South Side, Long Island, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Martin, Homer Dodge, 1488CY: A Glimpse of the Sea (Newport), 1925, 1985-1986 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Martin, Homer Dodge, 5096RY: An Island in the Adirondacks, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Mason, William Sanford, 8934CY: Caught Napping, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Mathews, Arthur and Lucia, 4987CY: Library Desk, 1996 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Matteson, Tompkins H., 3284CY: The Mayflower Compact, 1991-1992 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Matulka, Jan, 771CY: Trees in a Forest, circa 1982 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Matulka, Jan, 1575CY: Still Life, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Matulka, Jan, 1777CY: Farm Scene and Nude Study, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Matulka, Jan, 1778CY: Tree and Rocks, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Matulka, Jan, 2004CY, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Matulka, Jan, 3352CY: Slovak Village - Turi Pole, 1991-1994 (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - Matulka, Jan, 6995CY: Untitled, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - Matulka, Jan, 6996CY: Nautical Abstraction, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - Matulka, Jan, 6997CY: Nautical Abstraction, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - Matulka, Jan, 6998CY: Nautical Arrangement, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 32)
    - Matulka, Jan, 6999CY: Still Life with Propeller, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 33)
    - Matulka, Jan, 7000CY: Quiet Cove, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 34)
    - Matulka, Jan, 7001CY: Boat on the Shore, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 35)
    - Matulka, Jan, 7002CY: Beach Scene with Boats, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 36)
    - Matulka, Jan, 7003CY: Landscape with Boats, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 37)
    - Matulka, Jan, 7004CY: Big Boat, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 38)
    - Matulka, Jan, 7005CY: Houses and Boats, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 39)
    - Matulka, Jan, 7006CY: Still Life with Propeller and Anchor, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 40)
    - Matulka, Jan, 7007CY: Village with Bridge, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 41)
    - Matulka, Jan, 7008CY: Island and Sailboats, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 42)
    - Matulka, Jan, 7009CY: Houses on a Cove, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 43)
    - Matulka, Jan, 7010CY: Houses on a Cove, 1999-2000 (Box 41, Folder 44)
    - Matulka, Jan, 7011CY: Landscape with Palms and Sailboats, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 45)
    - Matulka, Jan, 7012CY: Gloucester Fisherman, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 46)
    - Matulka, Jan, 7013CY: New England Cove, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 47)
    - Matulka, Jan, 7014CY: Buildings and Boats, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 48)
    - Matulka, Jan, 7015CY: Still Life with Anchor and Capstan, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 49)
    - Matulka, Jan, 7016CY: View Along the Hudson River (Storm King Mountain), 1999 (Box 41, Folder 50)
    - Matulka, Jan, 7017CY: Cove With Lighthouse, 1999, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 51)
    - Matulka, Jan, 7018CY: City Island, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 52)
    - Matulka, Jan, 7019CY: Old Boat and Houses, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 53)
    - Matulka, Jan, 7020CY: The Backwater, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 54)
    - Matulka, Jan, 7021CY: Beach Scene Composition, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 55)
    - Matulka, Jan, 7022CY: Two Boats in a Cove, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 56)
    - Matulka, Jan, 7042CY: Cityscape, 1999-2000 (Box 41, Folder 57)
    - Matulka, Jan, 7046CY: Czech Horseman in Festival Garb, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 58)
    - Matulka, Jan, 7047CY: New England Landscape, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 59)
    - Matulka, Jan, 7048CY: Bronco Buster, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 60)
    - Matulka, Jan, 7053CY: Still Life with Pineapples, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 61)
    - Matulka, Jan, 7106CY: The White Oak, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 62)
    - Maurer, Alfred Henry, 480CY: Still Life with Red Flowers, 1981, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 63)
    - Maurer, Alfred Henry, 486CY: Still Life with Apple and Roll, 1981-1982 (Box 41, Folder 64)
    - Maurer, Alfred Henry, 1964CY: Vase of Flowers, 1987-1989 (Box 41, Folder 65)
    - Maurer, Alfred Henry, 2719JY: Flowers in a Vase, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 66)
    - Maurer, Alfred Henry, 3833CY: Still Life with Red Flowers, 1993, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 67)
    - Maurer, Alfred Henry, 4040CY: River Landscape, 1993-1994 (Box 41, Folder 68)
    - Maurer, Alfred Henry, 4592LY: Vertical Abstract Still Life, circa 1995 (Box 41, Folder 69)
    - Maurer, Alfred Henry, 6525JY: Still Life with Croissant, 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 70)
    - Maurer, Alfred Henry, 8784CY: Still Life, 2002-2003 (Box 41, Folder 71)
    - Maurer, Louis, 4906CY: Game of the North Woods, 1996 (Box 41, Folder 72)
    - Mayer, Frank Blackwell, 4910CY: Burritt's Study, 1996-1999 (Box 41, Folder 73)
    - Mazzanovich, Lawrence, 3953CY: Landscape, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 74)
    - Mazzanovich, Lawrence, 4517CY: October, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 75)
    - McCloskey, Alberta Binford, 1530CY: Pink Roses, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 76)
    - McCloskey, Alberta Binford, 4949CY: Roses on a Table, 1996 (Box 41, Folder 77)
    - McCloskey, William J., 5012CY: Oranges in Tissue Paper, 1996 (Box 41, Folder 78)
    - McCloskey, William J., 6344CY: Strawberries in Overturned Glass Bowl, 1996-1999 (Box 41, Folder 79)
    - McComas, Francis, 5016CY: Oak Tree, 1996 (Box 41, Folder 80)
    - McCord, George Herbert, 2668RY: Autumn, 1989, 1994-1995 (Box 41, Folder 81)
    - McCord, George Herbert, 4509CY: A View of Lake George, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 82)
    - McEntee, Jervis, 4092CY, 4092aCY: The Departure and The Return (Pair), 1993-1994 (Box 41, Folder 83)
    - McEntee, Jervis, 4116CY: Forest Interior, 1994-1995 (Box 41, Folder 84)
    - McEntee, Jervis, 4336CY: Journey's Pause on Roman Campagna, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 85)
    - McEntee, Jervis, 4341CY: River in the Forest, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 86)
    - McFee, Henry Lee, 494CY: Cubist Landscape, 1981-1982 (Box 41, Folder 87)
    - McFee, Henry Lee, 3815CY: Arizona Landscape, 1993, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 88)
    - McFee, Henry Lee, 4754CY: Buildings Bellevue, 1996-2002 (Box 41, Folder 89)
    - McFee, Henry Lee, 8506RY: Still Life, 2002-2003 (Box 41, Folder 90)
    - McLaughlin, John, 8941CY: Untitled, 2002-2003 (Box 41, Folder 91)
    - Mead, Horation Nelson, 1333CY: Two Log Books from the Ship Lacedaemonian, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 92)
    - Meade, Francis, 170CY: Steamers on the River, 1981, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 93)
    - Mechau, Frank, 4359CY: Dangers of the Mail and Pony Express (Pair), 1994-1995 (Box 41, Folder 94)
    - Meeker, Joseph Rusling, 1108CY: Morning on the Upper Mississippi, 1983-1984 (Box 41, Folder 95)
    - Meeker, Joseph Rusling, 1461CY: Morning in the Bayou, 1985-1989 (Box 41, Folder 96)
    - Melchers, Gari, 9158CY: Artist's Studio in Snow, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 97)
    - Mellen, Mary, 1874CY: Norman's Woe, Gloucester, Massachusetts, 1986-1987 (Box 41, Folder 98)
    - Mellen, Mary, 3045CY: Norman's Woe, Gloucester, Massachusetts, 1990-1991 (Box 41, Folder 99)
    - Mellen, Mary, 3390LY: Norman's Woe, Gloucester, Massachusetts, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 100)
    - Mellen, Mary, 3421CY: Ships Off Halfway Rock, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 101)
    - Melrose, Andrew, 144CY: Rockland Lake, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 102)
    - Melrose, Andrew, 200CY: Hudson River with Train, 1981-1982 (Box 41, Folder 103)
    - Melrose, Andrew, 1992CY: The Farmhouse, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 104)
    - Melrose, Andrew, 2617CY: The Picnic, 1988-1990 (Box 41, Folder 105)
    - Melrose, Andrew, 4581CY: View of Washington, D.C., 1995-1996 (Box 41, Folder 106)
    - Merrild, Knud, 4988CY: Aesthetic Function in Space, 1996 (Box 41, Folder 107)
    - Metcalf, Willard LeRoy, 767CY: Budding Oak, 1982-1983 (Box 41, Folder 108)
    - Metcalf, Willard LeRoy, 1612CY: Landscape at Giverny, 1985-1986 (Box 41, Folder 109)
    - Metcalf, Willard LeRoy, 2013CY: Monet's Formal Garden, 1982-1987 (Box 41, Folder 110)
    - Metcalf, Willard LeRoy, 3083CY: Trees, 1990-1999 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Metcalf, Willard LeRoy, 3948CY: Across the Harbor, 1993, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Metcalf, Willard LeRoy, 4473CY: Icebound Brook (Winter's Mantle), 1995 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Metcalf, Willard LeRoy, 4597CY: April Morning #1, 1995-1996 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Metcalf, Willard LeRoy, 4782CY: Cherry Blossoms, 1996 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Metcalf, Willard LeRoy, 7448LY: Landscape in Grez, France, 2000-2001 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Metcalf, Willard LeRoy, 7647CY: Brook in Vermont, 1997, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Meurer, Charles Alfred, 3540CY: Still Life with Books, Candle, Letters, Wine Glass, Cigarette, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Meyers, Albert, 2598RY: Cake Walk, 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Mignot, Louis Remy, 111CY: On the Guayaquil, 1983-1984 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Mignot, Louis Remy, 2309RY: On the Orinoco, Venezuela, 1988, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Mignot, Louis Remy, 2319CY: Sunset in the Forest, 1988-1993 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Mignot, Louis Remy, 2521RY: Winter Landscape, 1988-1995 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Mignot, Louis Remy, 3112CY: Latin American Landscape, 1990-1996 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Mignot, Louis Remy, 6240RY: Twilight on the Passaic, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Mignot, Louis Remy, 7040CY: The Day's Departure, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Millar, Addison Thomas, 6751RY: The Brass Hookah, 1998, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Millar, Addison Thomas, 7056JY: East Hampton, Long Island, 1999-2000 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Millar, Addison Thomas, 8561CY: Landscape, 2002, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Miller, A.J. (Attributed): (Painting of Indian Girl), 1983-1984 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Miller, Charles Frederic, 1168CY: California Landscape, 1984, 1996 (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Miller, Franklin H., 3424CY: Table Top Still Life: Peaches, Plums, Grapes and Pears, 1991-1992 (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - Miller, Richard Emile: Lady with a Gold Fan, circa 1981-2004 (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - Miller, Richard Emile, 870CY: After Tea, 1982-1983 (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - Miller, Richard Emile, 2732CY: Spring, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - Miller, Richard Emile, 4506CY: Sunlight and Snow, 1984, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - Miller, Richard Emile, 4573CY: The Artist's Wife, 1995-1997 (Box 42, Folder 27)
    - Miller, Richard Emile, 5060CY: Reclining Nude, 1996-1997 (Box 42, Folder 28)
    - Miller, William Rickaby: New York From Weehawken, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 29)
    - Miller, William Rickaby, 1508CY: A Village on Long Island, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 30)
    - Miller, William Rickaby, 1871CY: Central Park, 1988, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 31)
    - Miller, William Rickaby, 2007RY: By the Lake, 1987-1991 (Box 42, Folder 32)
    - Miller, William Rickaby, 3923CY: Gathering Faggots in the Snow, 1993-1994 (Box 42, Folder 33)
    - Miller, William Rickaby, 4013CY: Pineapples (Pair), 1993-1999 (Box 42, Folder 34)
    - Miller, William Rickaby, 4110CY: Still Life with Pineapples, Grapes and Geranium, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 35)
    - Miller, William Rickaby, 4180CY: New York from Weehawken, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 36)
    - Miller, William Rickaby, 4439CY: Crossing the Ford at Esops, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 37)
    - Miller, William Rickaby, 6627CY: Holiday in the Woods, 1998-1999 (Box 42, Folder 38)
    - Millet, Francis David, 212CY: The Tender Chord, 1981-1983 (Box 42, Folder 39)
    - Millet, Francis David, 675CY: Thesmophoria, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 40)
    - Millet, Francis David, 1589CY: Turkish Waterseller, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 41)
    - Millet, Francis David, 1722RY: The Artist's Bedroom, Antwerp, 1983-2000 (Box 42, Folder 42)
    - Millet, Francis David, 2703RY: The Poppy Field, 1976-2004 (Box 42, Folder 43)
    - Millet, Francis David, 2859RY: Swedish Kitchen, 1989-1993 (Box 42, Folder 44)
    - Millet, Francis Davis, 6032CY: Palm Trees - Capri, 1997, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 45)
    - Millet, Francis Davis, 8827CY: The Artist's Kitchen, Antwerp, 2002, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 46)
    - Minott, J.O., 6241CY: The Launching of Defender, 1995, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 47)
    - Mitchell, Joan, 3194CY: Composition, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 48)
    - Mitchell, William, 1585CY: Stag Hound's Head, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 49)
    - Moeller, Louis, 3991CY: Puzzled, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 50)
    - Monks, John Austin Sands, 6576RY: Merino Ram, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 51)
    - Mora, F. Luis, 8999CY: Picnic Scene, 2002, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 52)
    - Moran, Edward, 902CY: Oyster Boats Beating to Windward, 1983, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 53)
    - Moran, Edward, 1536RY: Windsor Castle, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 54)
    - Moran, Edward, 1972CY: Sailing in the New York Harbor, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 55)
    - Moran, Edward, 2475CY: Seascape, 1988-1989 (Box 42, Folder 56)
    - Moran, Edward, 2663CY: A View of New York Harbor, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 57)
    - Moran, Edward, 3027RY: Steeple Rock, Bar Harbor, Maine, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 58)
    - Moran, Edward, 3712CY: Seascape, Moonlight, 1992, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 59)
    - Moran, Edward, 3720CY: Windsor Castle, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 60)
    - Moran, Edward, 4496CY: Hove-to for a Pilot, 1995-1996 (Box 42, Folder 61)
    - Moran, Leon, 251CY: The First Robin, 1981-1982 (Box 42, Folder 62)
    - Moran, Paul Nimmo, 1431CY: By the Window, 1984-1986, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 63)
    - Moran, Thomas, 114CY: Orizaba, Mexico, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 64)
    - Moran, Thomas, 141CY: Moravatio, Mexico, 1981-1984 (Box 42, Folder 65)
    - Moran, Thomas, 275RY: View of Mexico City, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 66)
    - Moran, Thomas, 837CY: Lowery Day, 1982-1984 (Box 42, Folder 67)
    - Moran, Thomas, 1580CY: The Much Resounding Sea, 1985-1986 (Box 42, Folder 68)
    - Moran, Thomas, 1597LY: View of Venice, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 69)
    - Moran, Thomas, 1599CY: Gate of Venice, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 70)
    - Moran, Thomas, 1726CY: View of Venice, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 71)
    - Moran, Thomas, 2750JY: June - East Hampton, 1987-1995 (Box 42, Folder 72)
    - Moran, Thomas, 2882LY: Morning: Outskirts of Venice, 1988-1990 (Box 42, Folder 73)
    - Moran, Thomas, 2939CY: The Town Pond, Easthampton, 1989-1991 (Box 42, Folder 74)
    - Moran, Thomas, 3918CY: Mill Creek, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 75)
    - Moran, Thomas, 3947CY: Green River Cliffs, Wyoming, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 76)
    - Moran, Thomas, 6242CY: Falls of Schuykill, 1997-1998 (Box 42, Folder 77)
    - Moran, Thomas, 6243CY: The Harbor of Bera Cruz, Mexico, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 78)
    - Morrice, James Wilson, 3769CY: Sketch, Venice, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 79)
    - Morris, George Lovett Kingsland, 364CY: Composition No. 14, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 80)
    - Morris, George Lovett Kingsland, 2289CY: Exile, 1988 (Box 42, Folder 81)
    - Morris, George Lovett Kingsland, 3063CY: Retention, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 82)
    - Morris, George Lovett Kingsland, 3289CY: Torpedo Station, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 83)
    - Morris, George Lovett Kingsland, 4113CY: Precision Bombing, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 84)
    - Morris, George Lovett Kingsland, 4115CY: Totem, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 85)
    - Morris, George Lovett Kingsland, 4172CY: Times Square, 1994, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 86)
    - Morris, George Lovett Kingsland, 4783CY: Urban Concretion, 1996-1997 (Box 42, Folder 87)
    - Morris, George Lovett Kingsland, 4784CY: Raft on Lake, 1996 (Box 42, Folder 88)
    - Morris, George Lovett Kingsland, 6905CY: Bank in Depression, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 89)
    - Morris, George Lovett Kingsland, 8956CY: Contemplation, 2002-2003 (Box 42, Folder 90)
    - Morris, George Lovett Kingsland, 9261CY: Target, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 91)
    - Morse, Samuel Finley Breese, 1464CY: The Greek Boy, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 92)
    - Morse, Samuel Finley Breese, 4322LY: Portrait of Mrs. Helen Lincklaen, 1994-1995 (Box 42, Folder 93)
    - Morse, Samuel Finley Breese, 4323LY: Portrait of Mrs. Thomas H. Hubbard, 1994-1995 (Box 42, Folder 94)
    - Morse, Samuel Finley Breese, 8997CY: Portrait of Thurlow Weed, 1918, 1925, 2002- 2003 (Box 42, Folder 95)
    - Morviller, Joseph, 183CY: Winter in Malden, Massachusetts, 1981, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 96)
    - Morviller, Joseph, 259CY: Winter Scene, 1981-1982 (Box 42, Folder 97)
    - Morviller, Joseph, 1503CY: Gathering Kelp/Manchester by the Sea, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 98)
    - Morviller, Joseph, 1504CY: Early Autumn, 1985, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 99)
    - Morviller, Joseph, 1505CY: Landscape on Spot Pond, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 100)
    - Morviller, Joseph, 1507CY: Gathering Wood in Winter, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 101)
    - Morviller, Joseph, 1521CY: Winter Scene, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 102)
    - Morviller, Joseph, 2925CY: Malden, Massachusetts, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 103)
    - Morviller, Joseph, 6842CY: The Walden Pond in Winter, 1998, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 104)
    - Moses, Grandma, 184CY: The Alan House, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Moses, Grandma, 210CY: Sugaring Off, 1981-1982 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Moses, Grandma, 3427CY: The Old Mill on Sunday, 1991-1992 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Moses, Grandma, 6599JY: Checkered House in Winter, 1998-1999 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Mount, William Sidney, 2815CY: Interior, House at Stoney Brook, 1989-1990 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Mount, William Sidney, 6886CY: Portrait of a Young Woman in Landscape, 1999 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Mowbray, Henry Siddons, 1615CY: The Harem, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Mowbray, Henry Siddons, 2305RY: Rose Harvest, circa 1893, 1988-1998 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Mowbray, Henry Siddons, 2866LY: Madonna and Child Enthroned With Angels and Cherubim, 1989-1990 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Mowbray, Henry Siddons, 3802RY: Oriental Interior, 1992-1998 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Muhrman, Henry, 1653CY: Wooded Landscape, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Mulvaney, John, 3630CY: Boating on the Potomac, 1992, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Mulvaney, John, 3631CY: The Paddle-Wheel Steamer on the Potomac River, 1992, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Munnings, Alfred James, 112CY: Ready for the Ride, 1981-1984 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Murch, Walter Tandy, 1005RY: Kohlrabi, 1983 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Murch, Walter Tandy, 3416CY: Still Life With Rock and Cloth, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Murch, Walter Tandy, 3439CY: Studio Still Life, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Murch, Walter Tandy, 3868CY: The Invitation, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Murch, Walter Tandy, 4785CY: Nails and Onion, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - Murch, Walter Tandy, 5027CY: Governor, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Murch, Walter Tandy, 5028CY: Lunar Landscape, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - Murch, Walter Tandy, 5029CY: Study for the Sounds of Silver, 1996-1997 (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - Murphy, Hermann Dudley, 2599CY: Clouds, Winchester, 1988-1989 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - Murphy, Hermann Dudley, 3641CY: Clouds and Water, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - Murphy, Hermann Dudley, 4380CY: Zinnias #2, 1983, 1994-1998 (Box 43, Folder 25)
    - Murphy, John Francis, 1519CY [1859RY]: Autumn, 1985, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 26)
    - Murphy, John Francis, 1574CY: November, 1985-1986 (Box 43, Folder 27)
    - Murphy, John Francis, 1652CY: Montiguy, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 28)
    - Murphy, John Francis, 2031CY: Woodland Brook, 1987-1988 (Box 43, Folder 29)
    - Murphy, John Francis, 6128CY: Autumn Landscape, 1997 (Box 43, Folder 30)
    - Muss-Arnolt, Gustav, 2533CY: Setters on Point, 1988 (Box 43, Folder 31)
    - Myers, Ethel, 1176CY: The Lecture, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 32)
    - Myers, Ethel, 1177CY: The Processional, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 33)
    - Myers, Jerome, 1008CY: Children's Outing, 1983, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 34)
    - Myers, Jerome, 3618CY: Children's Outing, 1992, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 35)
    - Nadelman, Elie, 1012RY: Androgynous Head, 1983-1991 (Box 43, Folder 36)
    - Nadelman, Elie, 2930CY: Standing Buck, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 37)
    - Nadelman, Elie, 4538CY: Idealized Female Head, 1995-1996 (Box 43, Folder 38)
    - Nadelman, Elie, 4539CY: Wounded Stag, 1995, 1997 (Box 43, Folder 39)
    - Nadelman, Elie, 4543CY: Wounded Bull, 1995, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 40)
    - Nadelman, Elie, 4786CY: Reclining Nude, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 41)
    - Nadelman, Elie, 6050CY: Dancing Woman, 1997-1998 (Box 43, Folder 42)
    - Nadelman, Elie, 6051CY: Two Women, 1997 (Box 43, Folder 43)
    - Nadelman, Elie, 6052CY: Woman with Poodle, 1997-1998 (Box 43, Folder 44)
    - Nadelman, Elie, 6053CY: Wounded Bull #2, 1997-1998 (Box 43, Folder 45)
    - Nadelman, Elie, 6577CY: Male and Female Nudes, 1998-1999 (Box 43, Folder 46)
    - Nadelman, Elie, 6870CY: Wounded Bull, 1999 (Box 43, Folder 47)
    - Nadelman, Elie, 7439CY: Dancing Figure, 2000-2001 (Box 43, Folder 48)
    - Nadelman, Elie, 7528CY: Resting Stag, 2000-2001 (Box 43, Folder 49)
    - Nahl, Charles Christian, 4996CY: Peter Quiney and the Mountain Lion, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 50)
    - Nahl, Charles Christian, 7520CY: Little Girl in a Doorway 2000 (Box 43, Folder 51)
    - Nakian, Reuben, 7619RY: Sea Lion, 2000-2001 (Box 43, Folder 52)
    - Narjot, Erneste, 4940CY: Self Portrait in the Artist's Studio, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 53)
    - Nevelson, Louise, 4591CY: Lovers, circa 1995 (Box 43, Folder 54)
    - Newell, Gordon, 4989CY: The Dispossessed, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 55)
    - Newman, Carl, 3920CY: Nude Under Tree, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 56)
    - Newman, Henry Roderick, 3107RY: Temple of Philae, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 57)
    - Newman, Henry Roderick, 3565RY: Temple of Philae, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 58)
    - Newman, Henry Roderick, 3598CY: Irises in the Garden, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 59)
    - Newman, Henry Roderick, 3696JY: Palazzo Vecchio, 1992, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 60)
    - Newman, Henry Roderick, 3774CY: Mount Everett in Snow, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 61)
    - Newman, Henry Roderick, 3775CY: Spring, Kyoto, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 62)
    - Newman, Henry Roderick, 3782CY: Athens (Pair with 3783CY), 1992 (Box 43, Folder 63)
    - Newman, Henry Roderick, 3783CY: Tuscany (Pair with 3782CY), 1992 (Box 43, Folder 64)
    - Newman, Henry Roderick, 4712CY: Wind Flowers, 1995-1996 (Box 43, Folder 65)
    - Newman, Henry Roderick, 6048CY: Venetian Canal Scene, 1997, 2000 (Box 43, Folder 66)
    - Newman, Robert Loftin, 3225CY: Christ Appearing to Mary, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 67)
    - Newman, Robert Loftin, 3226CY: Pan in a Forest Clearing, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 68)
    - Newman, Robert Loftin, 3227CY: Woman Bathing by a Waterfall, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 69)
    - Newman, Robert Loftin, 3228CY: Woman and Child, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 70)
    - Newman, Robert Loftin, 3229CY: Woman Carrying a Child, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 71)
    - Newman, Robert Loftin, 3230CY: A Troubadour Playing a Lute, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 72)
    - Nichols, Burr H., 4135LY: (Tree Over Stream), 1994 (Box 43, Folder 73)
    - Nichols, Dale, 4761CY: Haying, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 74)
    - Nicholson, George W., 260CY: Four Cold Feet, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 75)
    - Nicoll, James Craig, 2927RY: Summer on the Coast, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 76)
    - Noll, Fred, 8989CY: Untitled Mobile, 2002 (Box 43, Folder 77)
    - Nordell, Carl, 4510CY: Child in Blue, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 78)
    - Nordfeldt, B.J.O., 503CY: Tangier, 1982 (Box 43, Folder 79)
    - Nordfeldt, B.J.O., 504CY: The Man with the Yellow Glove, 1982 (Box 43, Folder 80)
    - Nordfeldt, B.J.O., 505CY: Eggplant and Grapes, 1982, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 81)
    - Nordfeldt, B.J.O., 506CY: Fruits and Pink Flower, 1982, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 82)
    - Nordfeldt, B.J.O., 507CY: Spring, Minnesota, 1982-1983 (Box 43, Folder 83)
    - Nordfeldt, B.J.O., 508CY: Fighting Birds, 1982, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 84)
    - Nordfeldt, B.J.O., 509CY: Barrier Rocks, # 2, 1982 (Box 43, Folder 85)
    - Nordfeldt, B.J.O., 510CY: Maine Farms, 1982 (Box 43, Folder 86)
    - Nordfeldt, B.J.O., 511CY: Mexico, 1982-1983 (Box 43, Folder 87)
    - Nordfeldt, B.J.O., 607CY: Fish, Gray and Yellow, 1982 (Box 43, Folder 88)
    - Nordfeldt, B.J.O., 608CY: Man with Green Hat, 1982, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 89)